

CONTACT ME AT

- Jln. Parengan Kali, RT.016/RW.004, Kraton, Krian, Sidoarjo, Jawa Timui
- widyaamala26@gmail.com
- github.com/widyaamala
- in linked.com/in/widya-amala

AREAS OF EXPERTIES

- Java, PHP, JavaScript, HTML, CSS Experience
- SQL Experience
- Laravel Framework, Bootstrap
 Framework Experience
- Adobe XD, Figma Experience
- Working Knowledge of Version Control (Git.)

OTHER SKILLS

- Advanced problem solver and fast learner
- Sharp analytical skill
- Have a solid understanding of analytics and the design process
- Have a solid understanding of testing, including performance, functional, and user acceptance.
- UX research experties

WIDYA AMALA S

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a fresh graduate in Informatics Engineering with comprehensive understanding of software development and design specializing in web-based applications. I'm currently based in Surabaya as full time front-end developer. I'm open to work for a side position to sharpen my experience and improve my skilss.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Web Developer

WAKIMART INDONESIA | March 2021 - present

- Ensure the technical feasibility for UI/UX design.
- Translate business needs into functional and appealing interactive website
- Develop and maintain user interface.

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Front-end Web Developer

PT. PETROKIMIA GRESIK | July 2019 - Sept 2019

- Become a team leader in the project to designed and developed the front-end of a portal event website
- Specified the context of users, specified the user requirements, designed, coded the designs, and tested the designs

PRE-PROFESSIONAL PROJECT

Web-Based Coworking Space Management System Development

EZO SPACE MALANG | July 2020 - Dec 2020

 Developed a web-based application to maintain the records of reservations, memberships, partnerships, event managements, space availability, and payment transactions

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Brawijaya University

Informatics Engineering | 2016 - 2021